♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
HQ transfer calling Car Alpha.
Car Alpha. Go ahead.
In three miles, you’ll meet up
with escort two as planned.
(SINISTER MUSIC)
Copy that.
You happy to be
going home, huh, Duncan?
I don’t talk to cops,
so save your breath.
Typical. That’s what you get
trying to be nice.
(YELLS)
Duncan, hey!
What’s going on? What’s up?
Pull over. He’s had
some kind of attack.
Car Alpha to HQ transfer.
Go ahead, Car Alpha.
Duncan! Hey, you okay?
What’s going on here?
Huh?
Following procedure three.
Momentary stop to assess the situation.
(YELLS)
Hey!
Roger, Car Alpha.
Standing by for information.
Car Alpha? What’s going on?
Come in, please, Car Alpha.
Peter Duncan escaped
from a police transport van
without any outside help?
Yeah, that’s what they
said on the radio.
You know, ever since David Copperfield
made the statue of liberty disappear,
nothing surprises me anymore.
What bothers me is that
the two police officers
who were guarding him
talked about a supernatural force.
You think XANA is involved?
Not a chance.
The super scanner doesn’t
show any activated tower.
I just checked.
I hope you’re right.
Imagine public enemy number one
under XANA’s control.
Talk about double trouble.
A public enemy?
What did this Duncan guy do?
Oh, nothing much.
Fine art theft, safe cracking,
kidnapping, bank robberies.
You okay, Aelita?
Yes, uh…
I just didn’t sleep
very well last night.
Don’t forget we have a math test.
You gonna be alright?
No problem.
(SINISTER MUSIC)
As you all know, the exam
covers the principles of division.
I hope you’ve studied hard.
Hey, Ulrich, what’s the last digit
of a number divisible by two, huh?
Zero.
Oh, yeah! That’s the answer.
Well done, mam!
No, that’s the grade
you’re going to get
if you keep trying to cheat.
Oh.
Well, Jeremie, is there a problem?
I finished, mam.
I see. Good work!
Excellent, in fact, Jeremie.
(STUDENTS GASP)
(GRUNTS)
(SHUDDERS)
Aelita, are you okay?
(YELLS)
Aelita!
(SIREN WAILS)
Okay, what have we got?
Adolescent. 12 years old, unconscious.
Very weak pulse, irregular heartbeat.
Put her in bay one.
She’s gone into fibrillation.
10 mils of adrexin.
Heart’s failing.
She’s going down.
Cardiac unit!
Clear.
(FLATLINES)
Nothing.
Clear!
(PULSING)
That kid’s got a real
guardian angel, that’s for sure.
So, how is she?
She’s fine. Don’t worry.
She’ll be alright, but it’s
an extraordinary case.
Can we see her?
I don’t see why not,
but not too much noise.
She needs to rest.
Don’t worry, doctor!
Everyone knows I’m quiet and calm.
How were your test results?
Completely normal.
Maybe it’s got something
to do with the fact
that you’re not really human.
It could be the virus that
XANA implanted in me.
Did you find anything, Jeremie?
Dead calm as far XANA’s concerned.
No activated towers.
Although the superscan
seems to have reset itself.
It’s not giving the right results.
Kind of like me.
I guess it didn’t study, either.
No class this afternoon.
I’m going to pay a visit to
the factory to check it out.
We’ll go with you.
I’ll stay here.
We can have a
girl-to-girl talk for once.
Hey!
What the--
This guy’s crazy!
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
Don’t move!
Put your hands in the air!
(CRASHING)
Hands up!
That’s exactly what I was afraid of.
What?
The superscan bugged up.
I’ll find out why in a minute.
The real question is --
can you fix it?
Well, normally, yeah.
But the debugging phase takes time.
I don’t know if it’s a minor bug
or something more serious--
Okay, okay.
If XANA’s activated a tower,
we’ll find it much faster
by going directly to Lyoko.
You coming, Ulrich?
Mmhmm.
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization!
All clear here.
We’re gonna have to
search all the sectors.
Don’t panic.
I’m calling up your
vehicles, guys.
Jeremie, how’s it going
with the superscan?
Not too great.
Well, anyway, you
might as well forget it.
No, wait! We found it!
Activated tower dead ahead.
Right I’ve got it.
25 degrees north northeast.
Nice job, you guys!
Now all we got to do is
bring Aelita here to deactivate it.
Okay, I’m bringing you in.
That’s great. Now what’s up.
Oh, no!
Can you hear me? Hey!
Ulrich! Odd!
Uh, Jeremie, not that
we’re in a rush, but uh…
Jeremie?
Taking your time there.
Must’ve forgotten
to pay his phone bill.
The funniest part is --
Hiroki says to my father,
papa, when I grow up,
I’m gonna look like you,
but with muscles!
(CHUCKLES LIGHTLY)
Aelita?
(FLATLINES)
Oh, no.
I don’t believe it.
Get a doctor! Quickly!
What’s wrong with
this darn supercomputer.
Uh, Jeremie, are you
gonna bring us in or not?
We’ll have to
manage without him.
Get ready.
One.
Two.
Three!
Ugh!
Aah!
W-We can’t be devirtualized.
The scanners must be offline.
What is going on
around here, anyway?
I have no idea.
But we’ve got a real problem.
That’s the understatement of the year.
Oh, this is really bad.
Huh? What is that!
How about…
a gigantic invisible eraser?
Let’s get out of here!
Jeremie, do something fast, huh!
Before it’s too late!
Come on! Start up, will you!
Jeremie, can you hear us?
We have a big bug here!
Ah--whoa!
Ulrich!
Aah! Help!
Aah!
Thanks.
Huh? No!
(BOTH SCREAM)
(FLATLINES)
(GRUNTS)
Finally!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Looks like Lyoko has
recharged its batteries.
(PULSING)
In all of my years as a doctor,
this is the first time
I’ve ever seen that.
Hey, we’re doing okay.
(BEEPS)
Oh, no. The nuclear
battery’s going dead!
The uranium in the nuclear
battery’s almost all used up,
so the supercomputer keeps failing,
and pretty soon
it’ll turn off altogether.
Oh, is that all?
Then we just have to change the battery.
A supercomputer is not the
same as a Game Boy, Odd.
You can’t just pick up a bar of
uranium at the corner store.
But isn’t there a kind of
emergency backup battery?
No. I checked.
XANA is dying.
And so is Aelita.
And all on account
of that miserable virus.
I’m gonna get something to drink.
Aah!
Hey, princess.
Is this the best TV set they could find?
Don’t bother trying to cheer me up.
I heard what they said in the hallway.
Jeremie’s disappeared!
But he can’t have left just like that…
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Aelita!
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Ulrich, it’s me.
Jeremie, where are you?
Aelita’s just
had another attack.
That figures.
I just turned off the supercomputer.
What?!
Peter Duncan is under XANA’s control.
He kidnapped me to
make me replace the battery.
That means that
Aelita is safe, too, then.
Fantastic!
Yeah, except that
once the new battery is in…
Duncan’s gonna try to kill me.
It’s room 117. Little Aelita!
The only way to get rid of Duncan
is for your to go to Lyoko
and deactivate the tower.
Get Aelita out of the hospital,
and get here ASAP.
Aelita’s heart can’t take
an awful lot more of this.
I know. So hurry.
Huh?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC)
This ought to do the trick.
Easy…
Please let Aelita still be alive.
You won’t get away from me!
Yumi, Ulrich, Odd,
are you there?
Tell me you’re there!
You’re there!
We’re in the scanner room.
Is Aelita okay?
Couldn’t be better.
Launch the procedure
for Yumi, Aelita, and me.
We’re gonna deactivate that darn tower.
But where’s Ulrich?
Here I am.
You didn’t think we’d let
you have all the fun
with Peter Duncan, did you?
Transfer Odd.
Transfer Aelita.
Transfer Yumi.
Virtualization.
You should see the tower.
Over there.
Watch out.
Kankrelats!
We haven’t seen
you guys for a while!
I missed you!
Laser arrow!
One down.
Hiyah!
Jeremie, we’re gonna
need our vehicles.
Your rides are on the way.
Aah!
Yumi, you’re down to 10 life points.
The vehicles are materializing.
Hurry up, guys!
We’re doing our best!
It’s no picnic out here!
There’s no time, Odd! Let’s go!
It must be your lucky day,
you little kankre-creeps!
Tower dead ahead!
Great.
Can you handle him?
I love entertaining guests.
Two monsters in view.
(GIGGLES)
-Orruha?
-Raaaah!
Aelita, jump!
(SCREECHES)
Run to the tower!
(GRUNTS)
Ulrich!
(GROANS)
Uh--whoa!
Aah!
Whoa!
Now, it’s your turn.
Aah!
Odd!
(LAUGHS)
Stay away!
A-Aah!
Aelita, time to
pull out all the stops.
Aah!
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
(SCREECHES)
H-Aah!
(CHOKING)
Tower deactivated.
Aah!
Hey, you okay?
“Peter Duncan was found unconscious
“in front of police headquarters.
“The police are investigating,
but for the moment
“don’t have any leads as to
how the escaped prisoner
ended up outside the police station.”
Even if we did tell them
the truth, they’d never believe us.
You’re right.
That’s how it is for unsung
heroes like ourselves.
We gotta act and win
and remain in the shadows.
I guess that’s what being
a true hero’s all about.
But someday, everybody’s gonna
know just how brave we are.
And we’ll reap the real benefits
and rewards true heroes deserve.
Hey, speaking of rewards,
I just saw Misses Meyer.
Uh-oh.
She gave me the results of the math test.
Great! What did I get?
8,650 plus 51 minus 10,000 plus 1,299.
You mean I got…um…uh…
Wow!
I got 100?
No. Zero.
Don’t worry, Odd.
One day, everyone’s gonna know
how “brave” you are
by not studying.
And you’ll reap the rewards
that an unsung hero
like you deserves.
But don’t hold your breath.
(LAUGHS)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS